Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures Documenting Basketball
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Women's basketball game videotapes, 1985-2003; Accession 2006-A-030
  - Wisconsin, 1991 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 40)
  - Lafayette, 1991 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 39)
  - CCSU, 1991 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 41)
  - UNH, 1991 January 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 41)
  - Columbia, 1991 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 42)
  - Cornell, 1991 Feb2; videotape (VHS) (Box 43)
  - Harvard, 1991 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 44)
  - Harvard, 1991 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 44)
  - Columbia, 1991 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 42)
  - Hofstra, 1991 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 45)
  - Hartford, 1991 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 45)
  - Lafayette, 1991 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 46)
  - Lehigh, 1991 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 46)
  - Duke, 1991 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 47)
  - S. Florida, 1991 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 47)
  - Iona, 1992 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 48)
  - Army, 1992 January 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 49)
  - Fairfield, 1992 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 49)
  - New Hampshire, 1992 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 48)
  - Brown, 1992 January 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 50)
  - Brown, 1992 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 50)
  - Columbia, 1992 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 51)
  - Cornell, 1992 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 52)
  - Dartmouth, 1992 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 53)
  - Harvard, 1992 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 54)
  - Penn, 1992 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 55)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 55UA)
  - Princeton, 1992 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 56)
  - Cornell, 1992 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 52)
  - Columbia, 1992 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 51)
  - Princeton, 1992 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 56)
  - Penn, 1992 February 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 55)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 55UB)
  - Harvard, 1992 March 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 54)
  - Dartmouth, 1992 March 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 53)
  - Northwestern, 1992 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 57)
  - South Carolina, 1992 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 57)
  - Middle Tennessee State, 1992 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 58)
  - UMass, 1992 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 58)
  - LIU, 1993 January 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 59)
  - Hartford, 1993 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 59)
  - Lehigh, 1993 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 60)
  - Lafayette, 1993 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 60)
  - Fairfield, 1993 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 61)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 61UA)
  - Army, 1993 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 61)
  - Columbia, 1993 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 63)
  - Cornell, 1993 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 64)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 64U)
  - Princeton, 1993 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 66)
  - Penn, 1993 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 67)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 67U)
  - Harvard, 1993 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 68)
  - Dartmouth, 1993 February 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 69)
  - Cornell, 1993 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 64)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 64U)
  - Columbia, 1993 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 63)
  - Penn, 1993 March 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 67)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 67U)
  - Princeton, 1993 March 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 66)
  - Dartmouth, 1993 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 69)
  - Harvard, 1993 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 68)
  - Columbia, 1994 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
  - Dartmouth, 1994 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 71)
  - Princeton, 1994 February 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 72)
  - Penn, 1994 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 73)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 73U)
  - Columbia, 1994 February 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
  - Penn, 1994 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 73)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 73U)
  - Princeton, 1994 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 72)
  - Princeton, 1994 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 74)
  - Dartmouth, 1994 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 71)
  - Michigan State, 1995 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 75)
  - U. W. Green Bay, 1995 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 76)
  - Central Connecticut, 1995 November 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 77)
  - Lehigh, 1995 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 78)
  - Bucknell, 1995 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 79)
  - St. Francis, 1995 December 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 80)
  - College of Charleston, 1995 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 81)
  - Canisius, 1996 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 82)
  - UNCW, 1996 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 83)
  - Fairfield, 1996 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 310)
  - Princeton, 1996 January 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 84)
  - Penn, 1996 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 85)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 85U)
  - Hartford, 1996 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 86)
  - Brown, 1996 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 87)
  - Dartmouth, 1996 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 88)
  - Cornell, 1996 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 89)
  - Columbia, 1996 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 90)
  - Penn, 1996 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 91)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 91U)
  - Princeton, 1996 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 92)
  - Columbia, 1996 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 93)
  - Cornell, 1996 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 94)
  - Hofstra, 1996 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 95)
  - Hartford, 1996 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 96)
  - University of Utah, 1996 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 97)
  - Idaho State, 1996 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 98)
  - Iona, 1996 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 99)
  - Army, 1996 December 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 100)
  - Howard, 1996 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 101)
  - Furman University, 1996 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 102)
  - Fairfield, 1997 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 103)
  - Lehigh, 1997 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 104)
  - Penn, 1997 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 105)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 105U)
  - Princeton, 1997 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 311)
  - Central Connecticut, 1997 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 106)
  - Brown, 1997 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 107)
  - Dartmouth, 1997 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 108)
  - Harvard, 1997 Feb1; videotape (VHS) (Box 109)
  - Columbia, 1997 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 110)
  - Cornell, 1997 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 111)
  - Princeton, 1997 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 112)
  - Penn, 1997 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 113)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 113U)
  - Cornell, 1997 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 114)
  - Columbia, 1997 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 115)
  - Harvard, 1997 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 116)
  - Dartmouth, 1997 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 117)
  - Slovakia, 1997 November 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 118)
  - Hartford, 1997 November 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 119)
  - UIC, 1997 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 120)
  - Kansas State, 1997 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 121)
  - UMBC, 1997 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 122)
  - Central Connecticut, 1997 December 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 123)
  - Brown, 1997; videotape (VHS) (Box 124)
  - Hofstra, 1997-1998; videotape (VHS) (Box 125)
  - Lafayette, 1998 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 126)
  - Lehigh, 1998 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 127)
  - Princeton, 1998 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 128)
  - UPenn, 1998 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 302)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 302U)
  - Army, 1998 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 129)
  - Brown, 1998 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 130)
  - Brown, 1998 January 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 131)
  - Columbia, 1998 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 132)
  - Cornell, 1998 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 133)
  - Penn, 1998 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 134)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 134U)
  - Princeton, 1998 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 135)
  - Harvard, 1998 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 136)
  - Dartmouth, 1998 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 137)
  - Slovakia, 1998 November 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 138)
  - Hartford, 1998 November 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 139)
  - Hofstra, 1998 November 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 140)
  - USD, 1998 November 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 141)
  - Illinois, 1998 November 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 142)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 142U)
  - Army, 1998 December 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 144)
  - Lafayette, 1998 December 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 145)
  - Navy, 1998 December 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 146)
  - UNH, 1998-1999; videotape (VHS) (Box 147)
  - Lehigh, 1999 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 148)
  - Penn, 1999 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 149)
  - Brown, 1999 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 150)
  - Brown, 1999 January 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 151)
  - Harvard, 1999 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 312)
  - Dartmouth, 1999 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 152)
  - Cornell, 1999 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 153)
  - Columbia, 1999 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 154)
  - Princeton, 1999 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 155)
  - Penn, 1999 February 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 156)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 156U)
  - Columbia, 1999 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 157)
  - Cornell, 1999 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 158)
  - Dartmouth, 1999 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 159)
  - Harvard, 1999 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 160)
  - Foreign, 1999 November 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 161)
  - Central Connecticut, 1999 November 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 162)
  - Hofstra, 1999 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 163)
  - Elon, 1999 November 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 164)
  - Quinnipiac, 1999 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 165)
  - Sacred Heart, 1999 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 166)
  - Hofstra, 1999 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 167)
  - St. Peters, 1999 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 168)
  - Nebraska, 1999 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 169)
  - Lafayette, 2000 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 170)
  - Lehigh, 2000 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 171)
  - Harvard, 2000 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 172)
  - Dartmouth, 2000 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 173)
  - Stony Brook, 2000 January 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 174)
  - Brown, 2000 January 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 175)
  - Hartford, 2000 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 176)
  - Brown, 2000 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 177)
  - Navy, 2000 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 178)
  - Penn, 2000 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 179)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 179U)
  - Princeton, 2000 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 180)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 180U)
  - Cornell, 2000 February 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 182)
  - Columbia, 2000 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 183)
  - Dartmouth, 2000 February 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 184)
  - Harvard, 2000 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 185)
  - Columbia, 2000 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 186)
  - Cornell, 2000 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 187)
  - Princeton, 2000 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 188)
  - Penn, 2000 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 189)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 189U)
  - Blue/White Scrimmage, 2000 November 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 190)
  - Netherlands, 2000 November 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 191)
  - Boston University, 2000 November 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 192)
  - Baylor, 2000 November 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 193)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 193U)
  - University of North Texas, 2000 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 195)
  - TCU, 2000 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 196)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 196U)
  - Sacred Heart, 2000 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 197)
  - Quinnipiac, 2000 December 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 198)
  - Hartford, 2000 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 199)
  - Lafayette, 2000 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 200)
  - Central Connecticut, 2000 December 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 201)
  - University of Albany, 2000 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 202)
  - Sidelights, 2000-2001; videotape (VHS) (Box 203)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 203U)
  - Highlights, 2000-2001; videotape (VHS) (Box 206)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 206U)
  - Binghamton, 2001 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 208)
  - Army, 2001 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 209)
  - Harvard, 2001 January 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 210)
  - Dartmouth, 2001 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 211)
  - Navy, 2001 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 212)
  - Brown, 2001 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 213)
  - Brown, 2001 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 214)
  - UPenn, 2001 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 215)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 215U)
  - Princeton, 2001 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 216)
  - Cornell, 2001 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 217)
  - Columbia, 2001 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 218)
  - Dartmouth, 2001 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 219)
  - Harvard, 2001 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 220)
  - Columbia, 2001 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 313)
  - Cornell, 2001 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 221)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 221U)
  - Princeton, 2001 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 223)
  - UPenn, 2001 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 224)
  - Turkey, 2001 November 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 225)
  - Quinnipiac, 2001 November 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 226)
  - Houston, 2001 November 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 227)
  - Bowling Green, 2001 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 228)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 228U)
  - Central Connecticut, 2001 November 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 231)
  - Hartford, 2001 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 232)
  - Boston University, 2001 December 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 233)
  - Lafayette, 2001 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 234)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 234U)
  - Albany, 2001 December 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 236)
  - Miami, 2001 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 237)
  - Highlights, 2001-2002; videotape (VHS) (Box 238)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 238U)
  - Sacred Heart, 2002 January 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 240)
  - Army, 2002 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 241)
  - Columbia, 2002 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 242)
  - Cornell, 2002 January 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 243)
  - Iona, 2002 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 244)
  - Brown, 2002 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 245)
  - Brown, 2002 January 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 246)
  - Dartmouth, 2002 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 247)
  - Harvard, 2002 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 248)
  - UPenn, 2002 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 249)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 249U)
  - Princeton, 2002 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 250)
  - Cornell, 2002 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 251)
  - Columbia, 2002 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 252)
  - Princeton, 2002 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 253)
  - UPenn, 2002 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 254)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 254U)
  - Harvard, 2002 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 255)
  - Dartmouth, 2002 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 256)
  - Slovakia, 2002 November 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 257)
  - Vermont, 2002 November 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 258)
  - Navy, 2002 November 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 259)
  - Albany, 2002 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 260)
  - Quinnipiac, 2002 December 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 261)
  - Northwestern, 2002 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 262)
  - Central Michigan, 2002 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 263)
  - Army, 2002 December 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 264)
  - Fairleigh Dickenson, 2002 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 265)
  - Highlights, 2002-2003; videotape (VHS) (Box 266)
  - Central Connecticut, 2003 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 267)
  - Maine, 2003 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 268)
  - Sacred Heart, 2003 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 269)
  - Brown, 2003 January 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 270)
  - Brown, 2003 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 271)
  - Columbia, 2003 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 272)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 272U)
  - Dartmouth, 2003 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 274)
  - Harvard, 2003 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 275)
  - Penn, 2003 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 276)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 276U)
  - Princeton, 2003 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 277)
  - Cornell, 2003 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 278)
  - Columbia, 2003 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 279)
  - Princeton, 2003 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 280)
  - Penn, 2003 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 281)
    - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 281U)
  - Harvard, 2003 March 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 282)
  - Dartmouth, 2003 March 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 283)
  - Austria, 2003 November 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 284)
  - Vermont, 2003 November 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 285)
  - Oklahoma State, 2003 November 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 286)
  - Boston College, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 287)
  - Brown, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 288)
  - Brown, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 289)
  - Bucknell, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 290)
  - Cassovia, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 291)
  - Columbia, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 292)
  - Columbia, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 293)
  - Columbia, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 294)
  - Cornell, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 295)
  - Dartmouth, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 296)
  - Hartford, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 297)
  - Harvard, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 298)
  - Loyola, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 299)
  - NCSU, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 300)
  - Northridge, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 301)
  - SU, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 303)
  - St. Joseph's, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 304)
  - Other women's basketball-related videotapes
    - Tonya Lawrence highlight tapes
      - 1988-1989, videotape (VHS) (Box 305)
        - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 305U)
      - 1989-1990, videotape (VHS) (Box 306)
        - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 306U)
    - Yale women's basketball team video, 1999-2000; videotape (VHS) (Box 307)
    - Yale women's basketball recruiting videotape, 1999-2000; videotape (VHS) (Box 308)
    - Midnight madness, 2002 October 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 309)
- Men's and women's basketball game films, 1975-1981; Accession 2008-A-049
  - Men's
    - 1975-1976
      - Fordham, film reel (16mm) (Box 1)
      - Brown, 2 (Box 2–3)
      - Holy Cross, 2 (Box 4–5)
      - Columbia, 2 (Box 6–7)
      - Cornell, 2 (Box 8–9)
      - Princeton, 2 (Box 10–11)
      - Penn, 2 (Box 12–13)
        - Use copy for boxes 12-13, 1 (Box 12U)
    - 1976-1977
      - Columbia, 2 (Box 14–15)
      - Fordham, 2 (Box 16–17)
      - UConn, 2 (Box 18–19)
      - Cornell, 2 (Box 20–21)
      - Penn, 2 (Box 22–23)
        - Use copy for boxes 22-23, 1 (Box 22U)
      - Fairfield, 2 (Box 24–25)
      - Boston College, 2 (Box 26–27)
      - Brown, 2 (Box 28–29)
      - Princeton, 2 (Box 30–31)
    - 1977-1978
      - DePaul (Kodak Classic), 8 (Box 32–39)
    - 1978-1979
      - Navy, film reel (16mm) (Box 40)
    - 1980-1981
      - Cornell, film reel (16mm) (Box 41)
  - Women's
    - Harvard, 1978; film reel (16mm) (Box 42)
    - Ivy Championship, 1979
      - Cornell (first round), film reel (16mm) (Box 43)
      - Harvard (semi-final), film reel (16mm) (Box 44)
      - Princeton (final), film reel (16mm) (Box 45)
- Men's basketball game videotapes, 1991-2007; Accession 2016-A-019
  - NCAA Yale Basketball highlights, February 7, 1991; 1 (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies (designated by a 'U' suffix in the box number), or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
  - Yale vs. Vermont, December 30, 1996; 1 (Box 2)
  - Vermont vs. Yale, December 10, 1997; 1 (Box 3)
  - Vermont vs. Yale, December 9, 1998; 1 (Box 4)
  - Yale vs. Vermont, November 21, 1999; 1 (Box 5)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, March 4, 2000; 1 (Box 6)
  - Yale vs. Vermont, December 7, 2000; 1 (Box 7)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, February 15, 2001; 1 (Box 8)
  - Banquet and recruiting video, 2002; 1 (Box 9)
  - CBS stories of the 2002 NCAA Division I Men's Basketball Championship, 1 (Box 10)
  - Dartmouth Men's Basketball, 2002-2003; 1 (Box 11)
  - Italy game 2, 2002; 1 (Box 12)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, January 11, 2002; 1 (Box 13)
  - Yale vs. Cornell, January 12, 2002; 1 (Box 14)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 19, 2002; 1 (Box 15)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 26, 2002; 1 (Box 16)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, February 1, 2002; 1 (Box 17)
  - Yale vs. Harvard, February 2, 2002; 1 (Box 18)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, February 8, 2002; 1 (Box 19)
  - Yale vs. Cornell, February 15, 2002; 1 (Box 20)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, February 16, 2002; 1 (Box 21)
  - Yale vs. Princeton, February 22, 2002; 1 (Box 22)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, February 23, 2002; 1 (Box 23)
  - Yale vs. Harvard, March 1, 2002; 1 (Box 24)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, March 2, 2002; 1 (Box 25)
  - Princeton vs. Yale, March 7, 2002; 1 (Box 26)
  - Ivy League Playoff: Lafayette vs. Penn, March 9, 2002; 1 (Box 27)
  - Pennsylvania vs. Yale, March 9, 2002; 1 (Box 28)
  - Bulldogs Coverage, March 19, 2002; 1 (Box 29)
  - Yale vs. Penn State, December 1, 2002 (Box 30)
  - Yale vs. Sacred Heart, December 5, 2002; 1 (Box 31)
  - Yale vs. Central Connecticut State University, December 12, 2002; 1 (Box 32)
  - NCAA Division I Men's Basketball Championship, 2003; 1 (Box 33)
  - Saint Mary's College vs. Yale, January 2, 2003; 1 (Box 34)
  - Yale vs. Old Westbury, January 10, 2003; 1 (Box 35)
  - Yale vs. Renssalear, January 11, 2003; 1 (Box 36)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 16, 2003; 1 (Box 37)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 24, 2003; 1 (Box 38)
  - Cornell vs. Yale, February 1, 2003; 1 (Box 39)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, February 7, 2003; 1 (Box 40)
  - Yale vs. Harvard, February 8, 2003; 1 (Box 41)
  - Princeton vs. Yale, February 15, 2003; 1 (Box 42)
  - Yale vs. Cornell, February 21, 2003; 1 (Box 43)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, February 22, 2003; 1 (Box 44)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, March 1, 2003; 1 (Box 45)
  - Harvard vs. Yale, March 7, 2003; 1 (Box 46)
  - Pennsylvania vs. Yale, March 14, 2003; 1 (Box 47)
  - Blue/White Game, November 1, 2003; 1 (Box 48)
  - 320 All Stars vs. Yale, November 11, 2003; 1 (Box 49)
  - Yale vs. 320 All Stars, November 11, 2003; 1 (Box 50)
  - Wake Forest vs. Yale, November 29, 2003; 1 (Box 51)
  - Yale vs. Bucknell, November 29, 2003; 1 (Box 52)
  - Yale vs. Sacred Heart, December 4, 2003; 1 (Box 53)
  - Yale vs. Fairfield, December 7, 2003; 1 (Box 54)
  - Yale vs. St. Peter's, December 11, 2003; 1 (Box 55)
  - Yale vs. Niagra, December 20, 2003; 1 (Box 56)
  - Yale vs. South Carolina, December 20, 2003; 1 (Box 57)
  - 2004 NCAA Division I Men's Basketball Championship, 1 (Box 58)
  - Practice tape, 2004-2005; 1 (Box 59)
  - Yale vs. American, January 3, 2004; 1 (Box 60)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 16, 2004; 1 (Box 61)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 23, 2004; 1 (Box 62)
  - Pennsylvania vs. Yale, January 30, 2004; 1 (Box 63)
  - Yale vs. Princeton, January 31, 2004; 1 (Box 64)
  - Yale vs. Princeton, January 31, 2004; 1 (Box 65)